In Toronto's
war on crime.
the worst offenders
are pursued by the detectives
of the Specialized
Criminal Investigations Unit.
These are their stories.
The arctic is crawling
with polar bears.
and they're hungry.
and Logan the Brave.
a six year old explorer--
- Six and a half.
Swings across
to the other side.
Unless he'd rather his dad
show him how it's done.
Oh. one's got his leg!
Take that polar bear!
You really think you could
do the monkey bars?
Not a chance.
Drinking
on the job. huh?
I was. Your husband
wasn't having any.
It's funny. that. uh. your
flask has his initials on it.
I'll get the car.
Come on. bud. let's go.
Not yet.
Logan. Right now.
Hey! Come back here right now.
Logan. get down from there.
I mean it.
Right now!
My arm!
- Come on. come on.
- What happened?
- Nell. it's fine.
- Logan!
- We're fine!
Can you get up?
Just give him a little bit
of space. give him space.
Hey you okay? What happened?
So between Logan's testimony
and the eye witnesses.
this case is cut and dry.
but. never hurts to hear
from a grandparent.
Grandparents are old.
I go by papa.
Sorry. My new intern
is a nepotism hire.
Marcy. just push the button.
The red button.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Oh. Nell.
Hey.
Can I help you?
Yeah. actually.
I'm looking for a rug.
Something that doesnt stain.
Yes!
Applaud for yourselves.
So. grab an ass and light some
grass as we prepare to screen
our first film.
And who is
the first victim it is.
Who's responsible
for this masterpiece?
Anyone? No?
Our first director is shy.
And... lights.
No. help! Help!
Somebody help! Somebody please
help me!
Shut it off!
What is this place?
You've never been
to the cinefile?
Uh. no. But. uh. can't say
I'm surprised that you have.
Henry.
And you must be
detective Bateman.
Yeah.
Ah. oh.
Welcome to Cinephile.
Toronto's premiere showcase
for the weird and the wicked.
And we now have a brand new
claim to fame.
Murder.
I didn't drag you down here
for some AI slop.
This is a genuine snuff film.
No. no.
no. please. don't!
Well. the aberrations
of the camera lens
reads like an older model.
high 8 maybe?
Shh. shh. This guy's not dead.
Not yet. anyway. It's a minor
concussion at best.
All right. Look at the way
it bubbles around
the quickly viscous quality
of the skin. That is not CG.
Darkening. coagulated.
that is the reaction
of skin to exposure
to hydrochloric acid.
Queasy feeling
you get from watching it.
that's hard to fake.
Shivers that run up your spine
when you realize
you've just witnessed someone
perishing before your very eyes.
Should we have another go?
No. uh. less is more.
Less.
This was a RSVP event?
- Of course.
We're gonna need to get the
names of everyone in attendance.
Sure. but everyone here
was at a wrap party
when that DVD was delivered.
How do you know when that was?
Because. like almost
everything great in life.
it was captured on film.
This was captured
on Cinephile's doorbell cam.
Two nights ago someone
dropped the DVD
in the festival's submission
box at 7 05 P.M..
same time as Les
and the other participants
were at the Spaghetti Factory
for the wrap party.
Yeah. we spoke to everyone
in attendance. but it appears
nobody has any connection
to the film whatsoever.
So if no one at the Cinephile
was involved.
why release the film there?
No. we believe the Cinephile
was just a vehicle
for getting the film
out to the world.
Exactly. If the killer
had posted the video online.
Mark would've already
had tracked him down.
So how do you leak something
without leaving a trace?
Get somebody else
to do it for you.
At the screening
one of the kids recorded
the video on their phone
and posted it online.
9.200 views and counting.
And Les plastered
the entire city with posters
for the screening. I mean.
the killer could be anyone.
As could our victim. We cross
referenced this image against
our missing persons registry.
So far no hits.
Until we know that
this film is real.
we don't even know
that this is Toronto.
Yeah. but if the film is real.
that liquid
is hydrochloric acid.
which dissolves all traces
of DNA within 72 hours.
Then we're running out
of time.
Our victim
is a white male.
Photogrammetry puts him
at about 6 feet.
But other than that. he may
as well have worn the mask.
Which appears to be home made
and is impossible to trace.
- You got anything on the watch?
- Yeah. 300.000 sold
in the past year.
- Can you bring the video up?
Somebody please.
help me!
Behind the scream. can you
isolate that. bring that up.
Yep. Excuse me.
Somebody please help me!
Billy Roland White.
please come to the office.
The murder happened
near a school.
Well. let's make some calls.
Find out what school
has a student named
Billy Roland White.
So the announcement
came from this school.
Takes a certain type
to kill near kids.
Yeah. schools are loud.
chaotic. Even if a kid
does see something.
who's gonna believe him.
You seeing this?
- Yeah.
Oh. you smell that?
Tripod's still
here. but the camera's gone.
Rug's new.
The film was real.
We had the sample processed
as quickly as possible.
but the hydrochloric acid
dissolved all the biological
matter. No traces of DNA.
Ugh. that is grim.
Were there any impurities?
Fillings. pacemaker. anything
at all that could get us an ID?
Found traces of iron.
chromium. and nickel.
but those are most likely
from the watch.
Other than that I wasn't able to
pull anything from the barrel.
Which is why I analyzed a sample
from one of the containers
that was left in the garage.
See. a civilian can't just
order hydrochloric acid
in these quantities.
in case they are
a crazy person in a mask.
Right. This would've had to be
purchased commercially.
And then stolen or sold.
The sample was 37 percent
purity. usually used
in steel mills. So I used
the lot number to track down
the manufacturer. This container
belongs to Atkinson Steel.
I can assure you
that all of our stock
is completely intact.
But if you'd like to learn how
steel is made.
I'd be happy to give you a tour.
No. that's okay. I already
know how steel is made.
I even know how
it degrades over time.
Water and oxygen causing
it to develop iron oxide.
But this lock looks brand new.
- Is that a bad thing?
- No. it's a suspicious thing.
Especially considering
this old lock was smashed.
We have pieces of metal
all over the place.
Well. you also have cameras
Show us some footage of you
replacing that lock.
and we'll get out of your hair.
Last week during the night
shift. I went out for a smoke.
I usually take a couple of laps.
But when I came back.
the lock was already broken.
And 95 litres of
hydrochloric acid was missing.
I couldn't tell that
anything was missing.
You could tell that
the lock was broken.
Please. I can't lose this job.
So you replace the lock.
You make it look like
nothing happened.
We need access
to those cameras. Javier.
I deleted the footage.
That. unfortunately.
is obstructing
a murder investigation.
Okay. okay. But what if
I know who did it?
He was driving off
as I was coming back
I recognized the car.
Ryan Gray. Creep used to work
here til they sacked him.
Creep?
He set the foreman's car
on fire. The guy's nuts.
I haven't seen
Ryan since Friday.
He borrowed my car.
so I haven't been able to get
to the grocery store.
but he'll be back.
He. he takes care of me.
By um. letting you sleep
on the couch?
Well there's only one bedroom.
and Ryan needs his sleep.
Anyway. he wouldn't want
me blathering--
Mrs. Gray. please.
We're worried your son might
be in some serious trouble.
We just want you to know that
if Ryan is guilty
of what we think he is guilty
of. he could go to jail
for a very long time.
Well. I shouldn't tell you.
but I did find a stack
of one hundred dollar bills
in his dresser last week.
How thick was this stack?
So as thick as a deck
of playing cards.
That's about 40.000.
Uh. is the money
still in the house?
It was gone the next day.
Shirley. could you tell us
if you recognize this balaclava?
Aw. of course.
I
knit this for halloween
when Ryan was a kid.
He used to be such a sweet boy.
Hey.
What're you doing?
We put out a Canada-wide
warrant. Ryan Gray's face
is everywhere. Borders.
airports. rental car agencies.
Still. the guy could be
on a greyhound bus to anywhere
by now. What about the phone
number his mother gave us.
No. it's a dead end.
He must be using a burner.
The money that Ryan's mother
found is bothering me.
It's bothering me
too. If I had 40.000 dollars
I wouldn't be crashing
with my mom.
That money's recent.
Do you think someone could've
hired Ryan to make that film?
And. if it was just a snuff
film. why wouldn't Ryan
choose a more transient victim
who no one might miss.
Our victim had nice
clothes. nice watch.
And a family.
Noticed this. and enhanced it.
Dad.
So. maybe this wasn't random.
Maybe it was a targeted hit.
Well then maybe whoever hired
Ryan also cast the lead role.
Hmmm.
Some good news
over night. They found
Shirley Gray's mini van
at Pearson airport. It's been
there since last Saturday.
That's only good news if Ryan
Gray did not get on a plane.
Well he's not on any flight
manifests. and we're using
facial recognition in case
he's got a fake passport.
I misjudged this guy.
I thought we'd have him by now.
I mean look at him.
he's wearing a damn tea cozy.
Okay. let's say that
this was a targeted hit.
Why make the murder public
in such a horrific way?
Well there's only two people
who know the answer to that.
Ryan Gray and the person
who hired him.
And we still have no idea
who our victim is.
He was thrown in the back
of Shirley Gray's van.
There must be some evidence.
some DNA.
They're still processing
the car. but they also...
sent this over.
The next time I see you parked
in this spot
I will have you towed.
Shefa shop?
It's a store in a strip mall
up in North York.
Hmm. the killer's pretty
far from home.
Maybe he was meeting someone.
Someone with 40k in cash
and a serious grudge.
Oh.
Patience.
Are you planning on
shopping in here?
Uh. ma'am we're the police.
I don't care if you're
the king of Siam.
This is detective Graff.
I'm detective Bateman.
What's your name?
- Esther Severski.
Store owner.
- Well. Ms. Severski.
Do you recall putting this note
on a tan mini van last week?
Thursday. After a week of that
Schmendrick parking in my spot.
I decided to put a note
on the windshield because
he looked very dangerous.
But it worked. because then
on Friday I saw he was parked
behind the furniture shop.
Well. thank you so much
for your time.
So Ryan was parked here
for a whole week.
Yeah. it doesn't sound like
he was meeting the man
who hired him. Sounds like
he was doing surveillance.
Maybe of his victim.
So he parks his car behind
the furniture store
the day of murder.
Closing in on his target?
Officers. Shopping for
a comfortable couch?
Brighten up the break room.
If only we had the budget.
No. we're here to inquire about
a mini van that was parked out
the back of your store
last Friday.
- Friday. I wasn't here.
Who was?
- New guy. David Barnes.
- Is he here now?
No. It's crazy. but he begged
me for this job.
and then he missed both
his shifts this week.
The last time he was here
he left the store unlocked.
Baruch Hashem nothing was taken.
He's all right. I hope.
Footage from
the furniture store.
Friday at 1 08 P.M.
This employee David Barnes
helping the suspect Ryan Gray
carry a large rug
out the back exit.
David never re enters the store.
So Ryan gets David
to help him move the rug
into the back of the mini van.
pushes him in and
incapacitates him somehow.
Maybe chloroform. maybe drugs.
That is a match for the rug
in the garage.
He helped the guy move the rug
he was rolled in. That's cold.
Pause it.
Zoom in on his wrist.
That's the bracelet
our victim was wearing.
Before it was dissolved
in acid.
I'm sorry. I don't
understand. Is David okay?
Are you aware of anyone who
might've wanted
to harm your husband?
No. I mean. David and I lead
very different lives.
He goes out a lot.
I'm usually with Logan.
or working.
You two back
from the store already?
- Nell. what's going on?
- Uh. dad. can you.
can you take Logan
to the park or something?
Hi. Logan.
My name's Henry.
- Hi Henry.
- Oh.
Have you ever been
to the arctic.
Yep. Have you?
Not yet. My dad's taking me.
Did you know that in Yellowknife
you can see the northern lights
for 240 nights a year?
Yep. And did you know that
astronauts can see
the northern lights from space?
- Woah!
- Woah.
Grab your glove. Logan.
We'll play a little catch
in the park.
Okay.
A left handed glove. I guess
he throws with his right.
Yeah. Logan's right handed.
But he shook my hand
with his left.
Yeah. uh. a few months back
he fell on the playground
and um. hurt his arm.
Sorry. where is David?
What am I gonna tell my son?
What have you been telling
him? Your husband's been missing
for four days
and you haven't reported.
David's been staying in
a hotel for the past few weeks.
I've just told Logan
that he's away working.
We've been having some issues.
What kind of issues?
Just growing
in different directions.
But we're working on it.
No. marriage is complicated.
Oh. guess this backs up the idea
that David liked to party.
Or perhaps he was taking
the split hard.
- Mmm. There's a laptop.
- I see it.
Let's bag it
and get it to Mark.
What's David's kid's name?
Logan?
Well. I'm in.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well that's not a man with
a lot to hide.
He's got three tabs open
for divorce lawyers.
Looks like he wasn't as into
reconciliation as his wife.
What about that maps tab?
Well that would be the last
address David ever searched.
My niece and Logan
are friends. yeah.
Kids never happened for me. so.
I don't know. I just. I pretty
much piggyback off
my sister's family.
But yeah. David and I ended up
taking Edie and Logan
to a few Jays games last year.
How 'bout them Blue Jays?
Nah. man. Too much heartbreak
for me. I'm a Cubs fan now.
I like the old ball park.
What's going on here? You have
a fight with your planter?
No. that was David.
So it wasn't a friendly visit?
Things have gotten tense.
Truth is. I wasn't a fan
of how he treated Logan.
Treated him how?
What do you mean?
So. a few months back.
we're at the playground.
We're tipping the flask.
And. um. David's really starting
to feel it. I could tell.
Anyway. it's time to go.
and Logan's not listening.
Typical kid stuff. right?
He goes down the slide one more
time. and David goes ballistic.
He grabs his poor kid by the arm
and he throws him to the ground.
He ends up breaking Logan's arm.
David's wife said
that was an accident.
If I got treated
like Nell did.
I'd probably say the same thing.
I'm surprised she even
confronted him about it.
but she must have. because
the next thing I know
he's at my door. drunk.
yelling at me. telling me
that I ruined his life.
- You call the police?
- I threatened to.
Got him to go away.
Nell tells us she and David
are working on things.
but she doesn't tell us that
David broke her kid's arm?
Why would she hide that.
Maybe Nell took care of it
herself. Hired Ryan Gray
to kill David.
and protect her son.
Nell. Why didn't you tell us
that David broke Logan's arm?
What. so you could question
him about it?
I don't want Logan
to relive that.
It took long enough for him
to get comfortable
to tell me the truth.
Or. maybe you didn't want it
to happen again.
You were finally going to leave
your husband. weren't you?
I'm guessing David wasn't
happy about that. you know?
I mean if he broke down
Sebastian's door.
I can't imagine what he would
do to you. to your son.
David had been in a tough
place lately.
He hadn't worked in years.
and I run this successful
skincare company. You understand
what that does to the male ego.
Did anyone else know
about the abuse?
Sebastian knew because
he saw it.
I had a hard enough time
telling my lawyer about it.
Your divorce lawyer?
We were filing
a restraining order.
David was gonna be legally out
of our lives.
I was gonna win sole custody.
I didn't need him dead.
I'll wave attorney
client privilege.
you can ask him yourself.
Look. I had David Barnes
on a skewer. Told him that.
Low key insisted
he sign over custody.
Nell was waving support.
it was a good deal.
She just wanted them
out of their lives.
But he got angry. Said the
courts always favor the mother.
- Is that what you think?
- Wouldn't have mattered.
Nell was financially stable.
and David had a history
of substance abuse
and violence.
- Who else can vouch for that?
- Valid. detective.
Believe women isn't a
recognized legal principle
in any jurisdiction. Nell had
recorded other incidents.
but we needed witnesses
to David's temper.
Nell didn't want her father
getting involved. but I felt--
You brought him in anyway.
Testimony from a grandparent
can win a case.
Did Nell's father
corroborate her accusations?
No. he was in shock.
and he left.
Did Nell know
that you were meeting
with her father recently?
Yeah. She didn't want him
getting invovled.
but I wanted to win the case.
Excuse me. Marcy! Dammit.
Nell was telling the truth.
She was about to get
full custody.
Yeah. but she was lying about
who knew about the abuse.
She knew her lawyer
spoke to her father.
Well. maybe when he saw what
David did to his grandson.
he didn't care so much about
custody. he wanted revenge.
Ah. the ancient guardian.
selfless patriarch.
How'd you react when you found
out it was your son in law
who broke Logan's arm?
You saw the statement.
How he pulled Logan
off the slide.
You know the force it takes
to break bone?
That's enough. Now look.
I spoke with Logan right after
the playground incident.
He said he fell.
Nothing about David pulling him.
But after Nell took him
to the hospital.
he came back with
a different story.
Suddenly it was David's fault.
Maybe he didn't feel
safe saying it
until he had assurance from
his mother that it was okay.
Maybe...
But there's something else.
When Logan was two
he fell out of his high chair
and had to go to emerge.
He was fine. but...
I felt terrible.
because it was me
who forgot to do up
the safety straps.
But in her lawyer's file.
Nell is claiming that David
pushed the high chair over.
So you think that
she's fabricating abuse?
Nell calls David
an unemployed deadbeat.
but I'm their financial advisor.
I was part of the decision
that David assume the role
of stay at home dad.
Why would Nell. or your
daughter. go to such lengths
to separate Logan
from his father?
Nell has been offered a very
good job in Chicago.
And David could stop her
from taking Logan
unless she had full custody.
I love my daughter.
But since she was tiny.
Nell has never let anyone
get in the way
of what she wants.
I can't imagine
you wanted to lose
your grandson to Chicago.
I didn't.
So I went to my lawyer to.
about David fight back.
Did David know you were
planning to help him?
No. I was waiting to hear back
from my lawyer
to see if we had a case.
But it was shakey. because
there was a witness claiming
David broke Logan's arm.
- Sebastian Mercer.
I went to see the man.
But he held strong with his
version of events.
- Sebastian?
- I need to talk to you.
In the middle of the day?
Why haven't you been
answering my calls?
Listen. I. um.
I need to tell you something.
- Is this about David?
- The same David who.
who you told me was abusing you
and Logan?
The same David who you needed
out of our lives.
huh? Are you gonna stand
here or are you gonna pretend--
Hey.
There's nothing to tell.
Okay? Because you don't have
anything to do with this. Right?
Right.
I hate that. Believe women
is so important.
If Nell's weaponizing that.
putting real abused women
at risk to get what she wants.
And what Nell wants is what?
Oh. her kid. A career.
Move to Chicago.
Oh. great city.
River runs backwards.
You ever taken
the architectural tour?
Of course. yeah. it's got
beautiful old buildings.
Like Wriggley field.
home of the Cubs.
What do we know about Sebastian?
He's a venture capitalist at
Quantum Echelon.
They've got offices here.
New York.
and Chicago.
We know if he was married?
Lost his wife
six years ago to cancer.
Look. we don't know
that Sebastian is lying about
Logan's arm. But if he is.
it's probably not about money
because the man
makes a lot of it.
- Exactly. so.
Why else does a man lie
for somebody else's wife?
The Cubs. huh? Chicago Cubs.
I wanted to wear a Cubs hat
in this interview.
but nobody here in headquarters
seemed to have one because.
well this is a Blue Jays town.
But you're rooting
for the windy city.
You know we could've
just gone to a bar
if you wanted to talk
baseball. detective.
Your work takes you to Chicago
quite a bit. hmm?
Did you know Nell Barnes
was moving to Chicago?
- I. um...
- Sure you did.
cause you're moving
there as well.
Seems you're in
a relationship. huh?
We were keeping it quiet until
the custody case was settled.
Or. because you were an eye
witness whose testimony
could ensure Nell gets sole
custody of her son Logan.
No. David was going to lose
custody because he was abusive.
According to Nell.
Well. she wouldn't lie
about that.
Oh. but you did. You know
David didn't break Logan's arm.
So did Nell's father.
So. did you tell Nell?
Yeah. She went through her
dad's email and found out
that he was retaining a lawyer
for himself and David.
And Nell's sole custody win
wasn't guaranteed anymore.
So you paid Ryan Gray
to kill David.
I don't know Ryan Gray.
Well.
That's a little odd.
because the last we checked.
you and Ryan...
were on the same highschool
D&D club.
You know. you don't
look like a dungeon master.
We went through your portfolio.
We know that you haven't sold
a share in six years.
but two weeks ago you sold 40k's
worth in a down market.
The exact same amount you paid
your old buddy here. Ryan Gray
to take are of David so you
and Nell could move to Chicago.
We have enough to take you in.
But we might be able to help you
if you can testify
to Nell's involvement.
She had nothing to do
with this. all right?
So you did it yourself. huh?
Didn't you.
Okay. listen.
I hired Ryan.
but just to scare David.
Just to scare him?
By putting him in a vat of acid?
That is pretty scary.
So why'd you want him
to film it
if you only wanted
to scare him?
I didn't. I didn't need a
video of what I asked him to do.
Well maybe you didn't trust
your D&D ally
to get the job done.
Yeah? You needed proof that
David was turned into sludge.
Look. he was hurting Nell.
And Logan!
He's. he's a special kid.
All right? He doesn't deserve
a father like David.
No. he deserved you.
Is that it?
You were sick and tired
of piggybacking
on someone else's family.
You could have the beautiful
wife. the kid.
and you would be a far better
father than David ever was.
Hey. Has Ryan
been in touch since?
I'm supposed to be meeting him
somewhere outside of the city.
- Where?
- I don't know. Okay?
The guy has been extorting me.
He sent me the video saying
that if I didn't pay him more.
he was going to release it.
So I panicked
and I stopped answering.
Okay. help us find him
and at least we can say
that you cooperated.
Sebastian. how are you
contacting him?
With our burners.
Got a location
on Ryan's burner?
I want to pick him up.
I want Nell in here too.
We gotta get
to the bottom of this.
Ryan's phone is frozen
at 29 Downing street.
That's Nell's house.
Mrs. Barnes
is your son at home?
Yes. he's in the living room.
Why. is something wrong?
Logan may be
in danger.
Sorry. Logan? Logan?
I was in my office. Logan!
Logan? Logan!
Logan! Logan!
- It's detective Henry Graff.
we need to report
a missing child.
Ryan's not reaching out.
He could get a new burner
phone anywhere.
So why does a kidnapper who's
extorting Sebastian
not reach out?
One of the officers
found an active camera
across the street.
The footage is coming now.
There goes the phone.
He knows exactly
where he's going.
Ryan surveilled David
for a week
before he threw him in a van.
This guy does his homework.
Look at Logan. He's got his
arms wrapped around this guy.
This doesn't seem like
a stranger.
What if Ryan's not reaching
out because Ryan's
incapable of reaching out.
Mark. pull up the video
of the murder.
Okay there's Ryan in the mask.
He's violent. desperate.
But David Barnes. our victim.
he just keeps getting back up.
But what if David overpowered
Ryan. Graff.
we never see the face of the man
going into the barrell.
David switched their clothes.
That's not David Barnes going
into the barrell of acid.
It's Ryan Gray.
Look at me!
Hey! Hey. take that off.
My face is cold.
Hey. bud. Want to go help me
find a lake?
We can go fishing.
- Sure.
Hey. Do you remember what
your awesome new name is?
Thomas.
What's your new name. dad?
It's still dad.
Okay. let's say David Barnes
is alive. he overpowers Ryan
the hitman. Knocks him
unconscious. Why kill him?
Why not just call the police?
A call was placed from Ryan's
phone to Nell's
boyfriend Sebastian around
the time of the murder.
Now. we believe that David
placed that call to find out
who hired the hitman.
and Sebastian picked up.
David realized two things.
The first being that Nell
had manipulated Sebastian into
hiring a hitman. and secondly
that Sebastian would
go down for it while Nell
got away scott free.
So he edited the video to fake
his own death
and dropped it at the Cinephile.
that way we'd be looking for
Ryan while David disappeared
after kidnapping his own
son. and that makes Ryan
look like a hitman gone rogue.
David did all of this just to
be with his son.
the person that everyone was
trying to take away from him.
Well. he's still a murderer.
We have the border on alert.
Helicopters sweeping
rural crossings.
Unless he's gone north.
You think he'd stay
in the country
that just issued
an amber alert?
If he's a dad who just
abducted his son.
how do you make it
a little less scary?
You make it an adventure.
Take Logan to his favorite
place on Earth.
- Polar bears.
- The arctic.
One of those northern towns
where everyone's got something
to hide and no one's
asking any questions.
Okay. listen up. people.
We need to turn those
helicopters north.
Have local law enforcements
search all parks.
and closed camp grounds.
Come on people. let's go!
Car's empty. John spotted
the car off the highway.
We're clearing this site. but it
looks like they're in the wind.
Survival gear is here.
So's ammunition.
Where's the rifle?
Graff.
Wow...
Look at that. bud.
What do you think?
Are we almost at the tundra?
Not quite.
But we'll get there.
David Barnes.
What's going on. Dad?
Hi. Henry.
- Hey.
- He's a police man.
- Don't come any closer.
Hey. why don't we just get
Logan away from the edge. yeah?
We'll just go somewhere
safe and talk?
The only danger to Logan is
you backing me into a corner.
David. we know this isn't you.
Oh yeah? You sure? Because
everyone else seems
to think that it is.
- David if you'd left Logan.
you'd be scot-free by now.
But you couldn't do it.
With this plan.
whatever this is.
How long can you last out here?
I know. I know.
See. tactical's got
their weapons trained on you.
'cause of that rifle.
And your son
is only inches away from you.
It's as useless to you
as a handkerchief
and as dangerous as a grenade.
So. we need you to put it down.
- Okay.
- Careful.
Listen to me.
The best thing that I have ever
been is your dad.
Now I want you to go with
the police now. okay?
Why?
Don't worry.
I'm gonna be right behind you.
Hey. Logan?
Come here. You come here.
Don't you worry.
everything's gonna be okay.
You're gonna hang out with
my friend Cathy here. okay?
Okay.
Atta boy.
Woah. David. you just
said you were gonna be
right behind your son.
Yeah. well it's better
this way.
Because she won't stop!
It wasn't enough that the lawyer
wanted to take my son away.
she needed to just
stand at my funeral
and just watch them bury
a casket of human sludge!
Hey. David. we know Nell
fabricated the abuse.
Her own father knows. Okay?
You're not alone.
And you don't know this.
but he was planning to help you.
He was getting a lawyer.
What?
You're not alone.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Cause I killed someone. I mean.
I didn't mean to do.
I didn't want to do it.
- I know.
- I got stabbed in the neck
with a needle. and then I woke
up in a horror garage.
and this guy. he was...
You think that I wanted
to just fight him?
Or knock him out and then strip
him down and listen to the skin
crackle in the acid?
Listen. I get why you did
what you did.
The only way for you to live was
for him to die.
So you could be
reborn as someone else.
Or I just wanted to be
with my son.
And now I can't.
She won.
- David. no. no. no. wait!
I know that you want
to protect him.
I know that
that's all you've ever wanted.
That's why you uh. taught him
to tie his shoes. right?
Taught him to look both ways?
That's why you held his hand
when. uh.
you crossed the street with him
on the way to a Jays game.
And from the moment he was born
you made a promise
that no matter what you would
always. always be there for him.
And if you break that promise.
part of your boy.
that beautiful boy. Logan...
part of Logan goes
over the edge with you.
There's no rebirth here.
But he's gonna hate me.
He's gonna be scared of me.
No he won't.
He loves you.
And he's gonna keep on
loving you.
Because you're his dad.
And David.
you're the only one he's got.
Don't leave him like this.
Oh my God...
What have I done.
Come on.
Yeah. we're clear.
Logan? Logan come here!
Hi mom. My name's Thomas now.
No. no that's ridiculous.
It's okay. dad. Don't cry.
Let's go.
If there's evidence that
she's involved. we'll find it.
But that would put both
that kids parents in jail.
difuze.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org